<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
      <title>Home on cristiangcel </title>
      <generator uri="https://gohugo.io">Hugo</generator>
    <link>https://cristiangcel.eu/</link>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
    
    <updated>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:52:01 UTC</updated>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Voice My Choice: when Law 194 is not enough</title>
      <link>https://cristiangcel.eu/post/myvoice-mychoice/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Oct 2024 10:52:01 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cristiangcel.eu/post/myvoice-mychoice/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;./post/myvoice-mychoice.png&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34;&gt;


&lt;small&gt;Promotional image of the campaign - by My Voice My Choice, fair use&lt;/small&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Guaranteeing free and safe access to abortion in all EU member states, while providing economic support to women in need, is the goal of the “My Voice My Choice” campaign. On the occasion of the International Safe Abortion Day, the initiative has gained unprecedented support both in Italy and across Europe.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://cristiangcel.eu/privacy-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Sep 2024 10:01:12 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cristiangcel.eu/privacy-policy/</guid>
      <description>The present information outlines the services used to provide the essential functionalities of this website, in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). By using our site, you explicitly agree to the use of technologies such as cookies and third-party services for the purposes described below.
Google Fonts
When you visit our site, your browser may send requests to Google&amp;rsquo;s servers to load the necessary fonts. We do not collect personal data through Google Fonts, but Google may gather information related to your device and connection, such as your IP address, to optimize font delivery and improve service performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Press freedom, does it really exist in the West?</title>
      <link>https://cristiangcel.eu/post/press-freedom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 12:20:33 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cristiangcel.eu/post/press-freedom/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;./post/press-freedom.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34;&gt;


&lt;small&gt;Protesters of the &#39;Free Assange&#39; movement outside the High Court in London, UK - by Alisdare Hickson, CC BY-SA 4.0&lt;/small&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Journalism is a complex and varied field, in which not all professionals operate with the same integrity. There are journalists who simply report official narratives and others who, with courage and determination, dig beneath the surface to uncover hidden truths. The latter can be considered the true heroes of our time, dedicated to exposing propaganda and bringing uncomfortable facts to light.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Links</title>
      <link>https://cristiangcel.eu/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 17:46:37 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cristiangcel.eu/links/</guid>
      <description>Detail of the Compass on deck of the Roald Amundsen under sails - by Bernd Fiedler, CC BY-SA 4.0 These are links to external websites where you can learn more about me. Feel free to follow me on social media and mainstream channels where I am present, even if I rarely publish content.
My social profiles:
Instagram: https://instagram.com/cristiangcel Tiktok: https://tiktok.com/@cristiangcel Author pages and books-related:
Amazon Author: https://www.amazon.com/author/cristiangcel Wattpad: https://wattpad.com/user/cristiangcel OpenLibrary: https://openlibrary.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Books</title>
      <link>https://cristiangcel.eu/books/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 17:46:19 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cristiangcel.eu/books/</guid>
      <description>A typical 1920&#39;s - 1930&#39;s desk - by J. Lim, CC BY-NC-SA 2.0 My literary works are the result of a deep and genuine passion for writing: to discover these works means to immerse oneself in rich emotional universes, where each piece offers a new perspective, provocative emotions, and, if one can grasp the hidden meaning, a chance for personal growth. Whether it is poetry or narrative, my literary works have the ability to touch the soul of the reader and provide a noteworthy literary experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debaptism: an act of freedom and self-determination</title>
      <link>https://cristiangcel.eu/post/uaar-debaptism/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 10:30:37 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cristiangcel.eu/post/uaar-debaptism/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;./post/uaar-debaptism.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34;&gt;


&lt;small&gt;Activists of the UAAR at the 2014 Commemoration of the Capture of Rome - by Sergio D&#39;Afflitto, CC BY-SA 4.0&lt;/small&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In recent years, the topic of baptism and its subsequent religious imposition has sparked an increasingly heated debate in contemporary society. More and more people are choosing to &amp;ldquo;debaptize&amp;rdquo; themselves, a symbolic act of liberation from perceived constraints often dictated by a social and cultural context influenced by religion, particularly Catholicism. This phenomenon reflects the desire to affirm one&amp;rsquo;s autonomy and reject a religious identity imposed from birth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://cristiangcel.eu/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 12:30:04 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cristiangcel.eu/about/</guid>
      <description>A picture of myself in September 2023 - by Heraclea Foto, All Rights Reserved. My name is Gennaro Cristian Celestino, known online as cristiangcel. I am a Psychology student and in my free time, I am interested in current events, activism, and writing.
In my spare time, I manage this little website, which is my personal space on the web, where I write articles on topics of interest to me, present my literary works, and offer my readers other types of content related to what I do or think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Copyright is a tool that limits freedom</title>
      <link>https://cristiangcel.eu/post/against-copyright/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jul 2024 14:06:03 UTC</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://cristiangcel.eu/post/against-copyright/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;./post/against-copyright.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;image&#34;&gt;


&lt;small&gt;The Pirate Bay, a famous torrent search engine - by Broblike, CC BY-SA 4.0&lt;/small&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In an era where information and culture are more accessible than ever, the effectiveness and fairness of copyright is being questioned. The reality is that copyright limits the sharing of knowledge and cultures, causing harm to all of humanity, especially to those living in poorer countries who do not have access to the desired materials. It is time to reflect on how this regulation, originally created to protect the author, is actually crystallizing works and ideas, thus denying many the opportunity to enjoy and contribute to a shared cultural heritage.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>

